Rishabh Tripathy

WER DEVELOPER

Details

Raipur 07470537527

rishabhtripathy@hotmail.com

Links

www.linkedin.com/in/rish-you

https://github.com/RishabhTripathy/

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Next Js

Reactis

Redux

Typescript

NocoDB

Daisy-Ui

MUI

Framer Motion

AOS

Tailwind Css

GitHub

Bootstrap

jQuery Wordpress

Shopify

Microsoft Office

FL Studio

Languages

English

Hindi

Odia

Profile

An experienced web developer with a passion for creating dynamic and engaging web applications, I am excited to bring my skills to a new team. Looking forward to work with an enterprising team that can help me acquire an edge over the usual.

Employment History

Web Developer, CrissCross Lab, Gurgaon

DECEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

Intern, Ducat, Gurgaon

MAY 2022 - DECEMBER 2023

Projects

GurugramPlots, Gurgaon

Worked-On:- Whole Frontend.

Used:- Next Js, Tailwind CSS, Daisy-Ui, , JavaScript, CSS. etc

https://gurugramplot.com/

Thea Homes, Manali

Worked-on:- Whole Front-end as well as admin panel.

Used:- Next Js, Tailwind CSS, React-Sliders, React-Date picker, Daisy-Ui, AOS,

JavaScript, CSS, NocoDb, Swagger API. etc

https://theahomesmanali.com/

Pagoda Centurion, Mussoorie

Worked-On:- Whole frontend of the website.

 $\textbf{Using:-} \ \mathsf{Next} \ \mathsf{Js}, \mathsf{Tailwind} \ \mathsf{Css}, \mathsf{REST} \ \mathsf{API} \ \mathsf{,} \ \mathsf{React-Sliders}, \mathsf{React-Datepicker}, \mathsf{Daisy-Ui}, \mathsf{D$

Javascript, Css. etc

https://pagodacenturion.com/

Just Home Stay, Gurgaon

Worked-On:- many frontend components under the guidance of my manager

https://justhomestay.in/

ScoreMe

Worked-On:- Many front-end components under the guidance of my manager

https://scoreme.in/

Portfoli

Used:- HTML, Css, Javascript, React Js, Tailwind Css, Routers, react-smooth-scroll,

Framer Motion, Netlify, form.io etc

https://rishabhtripathy.netlify.app/

Artist Profile, Gurugram

https://rishabhtripathymusic.vercel.app/

Education

BSC in Electronic Media, Kushabhau Thakre University, Raipur

JULY 2018 - DECEMBER 202

SSC, Krishna Public School, Raipur

AUGUST 2014 - AUGUST 2015

HSC (Maths), BSS Pranavananda Academy, Raipur

AUGUST 2016 - AUGUST 2017